Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Trustees Weekend Working Papers and Minutes, 1995 -- 2019; UA003.017; 2.4 Linear Feet; 45 Digital Object(s) Containing 7893 files; 7.92 Gigabytes
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1902 -- 1998; UA003.017.083.00017 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [1 of 2], 1905 -- 1998; UA003.017.083.00018 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [2 of 2], 1905 -- 1998; UA003.017.083.00019 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1911 -- 1998; UA003.017.083.00020 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Board of Trustees Tuft University [Working papers and minutes] [Binder], 1911 -- 1998; UA003.017.083.00021 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustee Weekend [Working papers and minutes] [Binder], 1902 -- 1999; UA003.017.083.00022 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1902 -- 1999; UA003.017.083.00023 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Tufts University Trustee/Commencement Weekend [Working papers and minutes] [Binder], 1905 -- 1999; UA003.017.083.00024 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1905 -- 1999; UA003.017.083.00025 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustee Weekends 1999/2000 Front Materials [Binder] [1 of 5], UA003.017.083.00026 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustee Weekends 1999/2000 [Binder] [2 of 5], 1911 -- 1999; UA003.017.083.00027 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustee Weekends 1999/2000 [Binder] [3 of 5], 1911 -- 1999; UA003.017.084.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trustee Weekends 1999/2000 [Binder] [4 of 5], 2000 -- 2002; UA003.017.084.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trustee Weekends 1999/2000 [Binder] [5 of 5], 2000 -- 2005; UA003.017.084.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [1 of 2], 1911 -- 1999; UA003.017.084.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [2 of 2], 1911 -- 1999; UA003.017.084.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [1 of 2], 2000 -- 2002; UA003.017.084.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [2 of 2], 2000 -- 2002; UA003.017.084.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 2000 -- 2005; UA003.017.084.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trustee Weekends 2000/2001 Front Material [Binder] [1 of 5], UA003.017.084.00009 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trustee Weekends 2000/2001 [Binder] [2 of 5], UA003.017.084.00010 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - TW_2000-11-03_CD, 2000-11-03 -- 2000-11-04; UA003.017.084.00010.00001
    - TW_2000-11-03_CD [preservation], 2000-11-03 -- 2000-11-04; UA003.017.084.00010.00002
    - TW_2001-02-09_CD, UA003.017.084.00011.00001
      Files from the CD that the Office of the Board of Trustees sent out to trustee members. May duplicate materials in physical folder, but not exclusively or inclusively.
  - Trustee Weekends 2000/2001 [Binder] [3 of 5], UA003.017.084.00011 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - TW_2001-02-09_CD [preservation], UA003.017.084.00011.00002
  - Trustee Weekends 2000/2001 [Binder] [4 of 5], UA003.017.084.00012 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - TW_2001-05-18_CD, 2001-05-18 -- 2001-05-20; UA003.017.084.00012.00001
      Trustees Weekend 2001-05-18
    - TW_2001-05-18_CD [preservation], 2001-05-18 -- 2001-05-20; UA003.017.084.00012.00002
  - Trustee Weekends 2000/2001 Back Material [Binder] [5 of 5], UA003.017.084.00013 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
    - TW_2002-02-08_CD, 2001-02-08 -- 2001-02-09; UA003.017.084.00013.00001
      Trustees Weekend 2002-02-08
    - TW_2002-02-08_CD [preservation], 2001-02-08 -- 2001-02-09; UA003.017.084.00013.00002
  - TW_2002-05-17_CD, 2002-05-16 -- 2002-05-19; UA003.017.084.00014.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2002-05-17
  - TW_2002-05-17_CD [Preservation], 2002-05-16 -- 2002-05-19; UA003.017.084.00014.00002
  - TW_2002-11-01_CD, 2002-10-31 -- 2002-11-02; UA003.017.084.00015.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2002-11-01
  - TW_2002-11-01_CD [preservation], 2002-10-31 -- 2002-11-02; UA003.017.084.00015.00002
  - TW_2003-02-07_CD, 2003-02-07 -- 2003-02-08; UA003.017.084.00016.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2003-02-07
  - TW_2003-02-07_CD [preservation], 2003-02-07 -- 2003-02-08; UA003.017.084.00016.00002
  - TW_2003-05-15_CD, 2003-05-15 -- 2003-05-18; UA003.017.084.00017.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2003-05-15
  - TW_2003-05-15_CD [preservation], 2003-05-15 -- 2003-05-18; UA003.017.084.00017.00002
  - TW_2003-10-31, 2003-10-31 -- 2003-11-01; UA003.017.084.00018.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2004-02-06
  - TW_2003-10-31 [preservation], 2003-10-31 -- 2003-11-01; UA003.017.084.00018.00002
  - TW_2004-02-06, 2004-02-06 -- 2004-02-07; UA003.017.084.00019.00001
  - TW_2004-02-06 [preservation], 2004-02-06 -- 2004-02-07; UA003.017.084.00019.00002
  - TW_2004-05-21, 2004-05-21 -- 2004-05-23; UA003.017.084.00020.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2004-05-21
  - TW_2004-05-21 [preservation], 2004-05-21 -- 2004-05-23; UA003.017.084.00020.00002
  - TW_2004-11-05, 2004-05-21 -- 2004-05-23; UA003.017.084.00021.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2004-11-05
  - TW_2004-11-05 [preservation], 2004-05-21 -- 2004-05-23; UA003.017.084.00021.00002
  - TW_2005-02-11, 2005-02-11 -- 2005-02-12; UA003.017.084.00022.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2005-02-11
  - TW_2005-02-11 [preservation], 2005-02-11 -- 2005-02-12; UA003.017.084.00022.00002
  - TW_2005-05-20, 2005-05-20 -- 2005-05-22; UA003.017.084.00023.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2005-05-20
  - TW_2005-05-20 [preservation], 2005-05-20 -- 2005-05-22; UA003.017.084.00023.00002
  - TW_2005-11-04, 2005-11-04 -- 2005-11-05; UA003.017.084.00024.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2005-11-04
  - TW_2005-11-04 [preservation], 2005-11-04 -- 2005-11-05; UA003.017.084.00024.00002
  - TW_2006-02-10, 2006-02-10 -- 2006-02-11; UA003.017.084.00025.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2006-02-10
  - TW_2006-02-10 [preservation], 2006-02-10 -- 2006-02-11; UA003.017.084.00025.00002
  - TW_2006-05-19, 2006-05-19 -- 2006-05-21; UA003.017.084.00026.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2006-05-19
  - TW_2006-05-19 [preservation], 2006-05-19 -- 2006-05-21; UA003.017.084.00026.00002
  - TW_2006-11-03, 2006-11-03 -- 2006-11-04; UA003.017.084.00027.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2006-11-03
  - TW_2006-11-03 [preservation], 2006-11-03 -- 2006-11-04; UA003.017.084.00027.00002
  - TW_2007-02-08, 2007-02-08 -- 2007-02-10; UA003.017.084.00028.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2007-02-08
  - TW_2007-02-08 [preservation], 2007-02-08 -- 2007-02-10; UA003.017.084.00028.00002
  - TW_2007-05-18, 2007-05-17 -- 2007-05-20; UA003.017.084.00029.00001
    Trustees Weekend 2007-05-18
  - TW_2007-05-18 [preservation], 2007-05-17 -- 2007-05-20; UA003.017.084.00029.00002
  - Trustee weekend files, 2000-2010; UA003.017.00001; 3557 Digital Object(s); 3.53 Gigabytes
  - Trustee weekend files, 2018-11-02; UA003.017.00002; 10 Digital Object(s); 13.41 Megabytes
  - Trustee weekend files, 2019-02-08; UA003.017.00003; 9 Digital Object(s); 7.81 Megabytes
  - Trustee weekend files, 2019-05-17; UA003.017.00004; 11 Digital Object(s); 11.09 Megabytes
  - Trustee Weekend files, 2019 November 01; UA003.002341; 38.3 Megabytes 12 files
- Financial and Investment Records, 1915 -- 1940; UA003.018; 4.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains reports and records related to the finances and investments of Tufts College in the first year of the Twentieth Century.
  This series is arranged chronologically by type.
  - Audit Papers [1 of 5], 1921 -- 1924; UA003.018.120.00001 (Box 120)
  - Audit Papers 1921-1924 [2 of 5], UA003.018.120.00002 (Box 120)
  - Audit Reports 1921-1924 [3 of 5], UA003.018.120.00003 (Box 120)
  - Audit Reports 1921-1924 [4 of 5], UA003.018.120.00004 (Box 120)
  - Audit Reports 1921-1924 [5 of 5], UA003.018.120.00005 (Box 120)
  - Budget Appropriations 1922-1923, H.E.A., UA003.018.120.00006 (Box 120)
  - Preparation for Budget of June, 1923; UA003.018.120.00007 (Box 120)
  - Budget 1923-1934, H.E. Averill, UA003.018.120.00008 (Box 120)
  - Audit for Year ended June 30, 1924; UA003.018.120.00009 (Box 120)
  - Budget 1924-1925, copy for President Cousens, UA003.018.120.00010 (Box 120)
  - Budget 1924-5, copy for President Cousens, UA003.018.120.00011 (Box 120)
  - Budget 1924-1925, copy H.E. Averill, UA003.018.120.00012 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1925 August 24, UA003.018.120.00013 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1925 August 24, UA003.018.120.00014 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1925; UA003.018.120.00015 (Box 120)
  - Budget 1925-1926, H.E.A., UA003.018.120.00016 (Box 120)
  - Budget 1925-1926, President's copy, UA003.018.120.00017 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1926; UA003.018.120.00018 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1926; UA003.018.120.00019 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1926; UA003.018.120.00020 (Box 120)
  - Tufts College Athletic Association-Audit for the year ended June 30, 1926; UA003.018.120.00021 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1927, 1908 -- 1927; UA003.018.120.00022 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1927; UA003.018.120.00023 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1927; UA003.018.120.00024 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1928; UA003.018.120.00025 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1928; UA003.018.120.00026 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1928; UA003.018.120.00027 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1929; UA003.018.120.00028 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1929; UA003.018.120.00029 (Box 120)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1930; UA003.018.120.00030 (Box 120)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1930; UA003.018.120.00031 (Box 120)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1931; UA003.018.121.00001 (Box 121)
  - Audit for the year ended June 30, 1908 -- 1931; UA003.018.121.00002 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1908 -- 1932; UA003.018.121.00003 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1908 -- 1932; UA003.018.121.00004 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1908 -- 1933; UA003.018.121.00005 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1909 -- 1934; UA003.018.121.00006 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1909 -- 1935; UA003.018.121.00007 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June, 1909 -- 1936; UA003.018.121.00008 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1909 -- 1936; UA003.018.121.00009 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1909 -- 1937; UA003.018.121.00010 (Box 121)
  - Examination for the year ended June 30, 1909 -- 1938; UA003.018.121.00011 (Box 121)
  - Tufts College Athletic Association- Audit for the year ended June 30, 1929; UA003.018.121.00012 (Box 121)
  - Tufts College Athletic Association- Audit for the year ending June 30, 1930; UA003.018.121.00013 (Box 121)
  - Tufts College Athletic Association- Audit for the year ended June 30, 1931; UA003.018.121.00014 (Box 121)
  - Tufts College Athletic Association- Examination for the year ended June 30, 1932; UA003.018.121.00015 (Box 121)
  - Tufts College Bookstores- Financial Statements for the fiscal year ended June 30, 1930; UA003.018.121.00016 (Box 121)
  - The President's Budget for, 1915 -- 1916; UA003.018.121.00017 (Box 121)
  - The President's Budget for, 1915 -- 1916; UA003.018.121.00018 (Box 121)
  - Tufts College Budget, 1915 -- 1916; UA003.018.121.00019 (Box 121)
  - Basis for Tentative Salary Budget, 1928 -- 1929; UA003.018.121.00020 (Box 121)
  - Budgets 1922-3, 1925-6, Inclusive, 1922 -- 1926; UA003.018.122.00001 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1926-1927, Asst. Treas. copy, UA003.018.122.00002 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1926-1927, President's copy, UA003.018.122.00003 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1926-1927, S.W.M., UA003.018.122.00004 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1927-1928, H.E.A. copy, UA003.018.122.00005 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1927-1928, Presidents's copy, UA003.018.122.00006 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1927-1928, S.W.M., UA003.018.122.00007 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1928-1929, book keeper, UA003.018.122.00008 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1928-1929, H.E.A. copy, UA003.018.122.00009 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1928-1929, President's copy, UA003.018.122.00010 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1928-1929, S.W.M., UA003.018.122.00011 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1929-1930, Asst. Treas., UA003.018.122.00012 (Box 122)
  - Budget 1929-1930, President, UA003.018.123.00001 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1930-1931, book keeper, UA003.018.123.00002 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1930-1931, President's Copy, UA003.018.123.00003 (Box 123)
  - budget 1931-1932, President's copy, UA003.018.123.00004 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1932-1933, President's copy, UA003.018.123.00005 (Box 123)
  - [1932-1935 Budget working papers], UA003.018.123.00006 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1936-1937, book keeper copy, UA003.018.123.00007 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1937-1938, book keeper, UA003.018.123.00008 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1937-1938, President's office, UA003.018.123.00009 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1938-1939 and working paper copy of budget year ending June 30, 1940; UA003.018.123.00010 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1939-1940, book keeper, UA003.018.123.00011 (Box 123)
  - Budget 1939-1940, copy no. 3, UA003.018.123.00012 (Box 123)
  - Budget, 1939 -- 1940; UA003.018.123.00013 (Box 123)
- Campaign Committees, 1996 -- 2017; UA003.019; 1.2 Linear Feet; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 zip files containing 143 files.; .15 Gigabytes
  This series contains material from Tufts University's Campaign Committees, including the Campaign Planning, Campaign Steering, and Campaign Executive committees.
  - Various committee files, 1996-2016; UA003.019.00001; 125 Digital Object(s); 0.14 Gigabytes
  - Campaign Planning files, 2016; UA003.019.00002; 8 Digital Object(s); 5.27 Megabytes
  - Campaign Planning files, 2017; UA003.019.00003; 10 Digital Object(s); 6.76 Megabytes
  - Campaign Steering and Campaign Executive Committee working papers, 2008 -- 2010; UA003.019.130; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 130, Folder 13 - 19)
- Student Affairs Committee, 2018 -- 2020; UA003.021; 8 Digital Object(s) 8 zip files containing 31 files.; 26.41 Megabytes
  Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
  This series contains material from Tufts University's Student Affairs Committee, including meeting agendas and supplementary materials.
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2018-04-26; UA003.021.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); 4.89 Megabytes
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2018-05-11; UA003.021.00002; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.33 Megabytes
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2019-01-29; UA003.021.00003; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.21 Megabytes
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2019-04-23; UA003.021.00004; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.74 Megabytes
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2019 October 25; UA003.002338; 3.9 Megabytes 4 files
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2020 January 22; UA003.002402; 1.99 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2020 April 30; UA003.002403; 10.05 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Student Affairs Committee files, 2020 November 20; UA003.002404; 2.2 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
- Additional accessions, 1851 -- 2007; UA003.020; 152.03 Megabytes This is the size of the three large zip files and does not take into account the other digital objects in this extent.
  - Meeting minutes, 1960 -- 2000; UA003-001 (Box 1)
  - Working Papers ("Trustee Weekend Materials"), 1992 -- 1997; UA003-003 (Box 2)
  - TNEMC and other subject files, plus the Tufts College Mathematical Research Project NAVEXOS., 1948 -- 1985; UA003-004 (Box 3)
  - Microfilm of Minutes and Reports, Backup Disks of Votes, Audio Cassettes., 1851 -- 1979; UA003-005 (Box 4)
  - Trustees letters and correspondence, 1890 -- 1950; UA003-026 (Box 5)
  - Bylaws, conflict of interest indemnification, Policy [binders], 1982 -- 1999; UA003-030 (Box 6)
  - Vote files [binders], 1982 -- 1999; UA003-031 (Box 7)
  - Letter and restated Articles of Organization, 1855 -- 1975; UA003-033 (Box 8)
  - Trustees Weekend and Executive Committee Binders, UA003-037 (Box 9)
  - Trustees Weekend and Executive Committee Binders, UA003-038 (Box 10)
  - Trustees Weekend and Executive Committee Binders, UA003-039 (Box 11)
  - Trustees Weekend and Executive Committee Binders, UA003-040 (Box 12)
  - Trustees Weekend and Executive Committee Binders, UA003-041 (Box 13)
  - Trustees Weekend and Executive Committee Binders, UA003-042 (Box 14)
  - R.B. Coolidge Real Estate files Box 1, 1900 -- 1950; UA003-045 (Box 15)
  - R.B. Coolidge Real Estate files Box 2, 1900 -- 1950; UA003-046 (Box 16)
  - R.B. Coolidge Real Estate files Box 3, 1900 -- 1950; UA003-047 (Box 17)
  - R.B. Coolidge Real Estate files Box 4, 1900 -- 1950; UA003-048 (Box 18)
  - R.B. Coolidge Real Estate files Box 5, 1900 -- 1950; UA003-049 (Box 19)
  - R.B. Coolidge Real Estate files Box 6, 1900 -- 1950; UA003-050 (Box 20)
  - Eppinger and Russell Investment Files Box 1, 1930 -- 1950; UA003-051 (Box 21)
  - Eppinger and Russell Investment Files Box 2, 1930 -- 1950; UA003-052 (Box 22)
  - Eppinger and Russell Investment Files Box 3, 1930 -- 1950; UA003-053 (Box 23)
  - Eppinger and Russell Investment Files Box 4, 1930 -- 1950; UA003-054 (Box 24)
  - Eppinger and Russell Investment Files Box 5, 1930 -- 1950; UA003-055 (Box 25)
  - Eppinger and Russell Investment Files Box 6, 1930 -- 1950; UA003-056 (Box 26)
  - Letters Jan 1908-Dec 1912?; Reports (taxes, etc.) Jan 1909-July 1917; Trustees Records 1903-1908, 1903 -- 1917; UA003-057 (Box 27)
  - Reports 1905-1906; Alumni/Prof Letters ca. 1914; Office of the secretary 1899-1910, 1899 -- 1914; UA003-058 (Box 28)
  - Treasurer's letters 1898-1901; Letters March 1906-Jan 1907; Letters Feb 1907-Dec 1907, 1898 -- 1907; UA003-059 (Box 29)
  - Letters Sept 1907 to Sept 1910; 1898-1900 Sept; 1900Sept - 1907 Sept, 1898 -- 1910; UA003-060 (Box 30)
  - Old Colony Financial papers, UA003-062 (Box 31)
  - Old Colony Financial papers, UA003-063 (Box 32)
  - Old Colony Financial papers, UA003-064 (Box 33)
  - Old Colony Financial papers, UA003-065 (Box 34)
  - Leighton Treasurer files, UA003-066 (Box 35)
  - Florida investment files, UA003-067 (Box 36)
  - Bursar and treasurer letters, UA003-068 (Box 37)
  - Fletcher estate and Old Colony investment files, UA003-069 (Box 38)
  - Real Estate files, UA003-070 (Box 39)
  - Acceptance/Declination letters, UA003-071 (Box 40)
  - Acceptance/Declination letters, UA003-072 (Box 41)
  - Acceptance/Declination letters, UA003-073 (Box 42)
  - Acceptance/Declination letters and handbooks, UA003-074 (Box 43)
  - Academic Affairs, 2000 -- 2001; UA003-076 (Box 44)
  - Academic Affairs, 2001 -- 2002; UA003-077 (Box 45)
  - Administration and Finance, 2001 -- 2004; UA003-078 (Box 46)
  - Board of Trustees, 2001 -- 2003; UA003-079 (Box 47)
  - Board of Trustees working papers (1 of 2), 2003 -- 2004; UA003-086 (Box 48)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Board of Trustees working papers (2 of 2), 2003 -- 2004; UA003-087 (Box 49)
  - Working papers (1 of 3), 2003 -- 2007; UA003-088 (Box 50)
  - Working papers (2 of 3), 2003 -- 2007; UA003-089 (Box 51)
  - Working papers (3 of 3), 2003 -- 2007; UA003-090 (Box 52)